Ms. Korrakorn Saiyood Developer







I am a dedicated developer who has 9 years experiences in the various kinds of software industry. My career objectives is developing the high effective softwares with software standard to serve all clients' requirements in the required time.

GENERAL INFORMATIONS

Date of birth

11 August 1985

Address

50/1, Chiangmai - Maejo Rd. Moo.5, T.Nonghan, A.Sansai, Chiangmai Province, 50290

Education

Bachelor of Science Program in Information Technology Maejo University, Chiangmai, Thailand.

Grade Average: 2.71

Work Experiences

e-Synergy (Thailand) Corporation, Bangkok, Thailand.

2007 - 2009

Nim See Seng Leasing Co., Ltd., Chiang Mai, Thailand.

2009 - 2010

One2Crowd Co., Ltd., Chiang Mai, Thailand.

2010 - 2014

CLBS Co., Ltd., Chiang Mai, Thailand.

2014 - Present

LANGUAGE SKILLS

PHP

- Use PHP5 to develop.
- Appointed for System Developer.
- Developed and deployed server side on Apache2.2 to server.
- Participated in system construction, analysis and testing.
- Maintenance SQL Server 2005 database, production and development environments.
- Software document creating.
- Provided maintenance to program users along with programming support.

JAVA

- Designed, developed and deployed server side Java and JSP-Servlet for software.
- Requirement searching on myself.
- Used UML to design pattern on software.
- Created database objects through testing, production and development environments.
- Used SQL Server Database for system and SQL to use.

C#.net Web Application

- Use .Net framework 2.0 to develop.
- Appointed for System Developer.
- Developed and deployed server side on C#.net on IIS to application server.
- Participated in system construction, analysis and testing.
- Maintenance SQL Server 2005 database, production and development environments.
- Use C# Application to coding for connect on OLAP, and use BIDS tool for IDE.
- Software document creating.
- Provided maintenance to program users along with programming support.

{FIN}

CMS

- Use Wordpress, Drupal, MAGENTO COMMERCE, Joomla! to develop web application.
- Maintenance MySQL database, production and development environments.
- Software document creating. Provided maintenance to program users along with programming support.

CMMI

- Payroll System (Internal Project 5)
- Appointed for CM (Configuration Management Position).

Data Analysis System

- Appointed for MA (Measurement & Analysis Position).

SOFTWARE AND OS SKILLS

Language:

- PHP (Zend Framework, Code Igniter MVC Framework)
- Java Script (JQuery Frameworks)
- Bootstrap Frameworks
- HTML, CSS Java 1.6, Java
- Servlet Web Application. (Sun Certified for the java 2 platform 1.4)
- Microsoft C#.Net (2 Years Experience)
- MDX Query for OLAP.

Software:

- GIT System
- Netbeans IDE for java and php
- Edit Plus for text manage tool.
- Eclipse IDE
- Microsoft Visual Sudio IDE for development.
- Microsoft Management Studio for SQL Server 2005.
- SQL Manager helper for SQL Query in SQL Server 2005.
- SQL Server 2003-2005-2008 Express, SQLite, MySQL.
- BIDS tools for OLAP (Business intelligence development studio for OLAP)

Operating System:

- Windows 7 32 and 64 bit, Windows Server 2003, Linux Ubuntu.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:

MY HOBBIES ARE SWIMMING, SEARCH INFORMATION IN INTERNET AND TRAVEL ABOUT ENVIRONMENT.